in the last lecture I used two Boolean
在上一节课中，我用了两个布尔值
operations Union and difference in this
运营联盟及其在这方面的区别
lecture we will look at the different
我们来看看这节课的不同
Boolean operations with Union you can
使用并集进行布尔运算您可以
combine different paths into a single
将不同的路径合并为一条
path here I have two circles and a
路径在这里我有两个圆圈和一个
rectangle with rounded Corners I select
我选择了圆角矩形
the three elements and go to path union
三行与行路结合
now I have a cloud the second Boolean is
现在我有一个云，第二个布尔值是
difference the Apple logo has a bite out
不同的是，苹果的标志有一处被咬掉了
of it the top Circle will be subtracted
其中顶端的圆将被减去
from the Apple below
来自下面的苹果
with intersection only the parts that
仅与以下部分相交
overlap remain
重叠保持不变
with just two circles you can make a
只需两个圆圈，就可以做出一个
leaf exclude does the opposite as
叶排除的作用与此相反，因为
intersection overlapping parts are
交叉点重叠部分为
excluded from the end result creating
从最终结果创建中排除
holes division is the same as
孔的分割与
intersection but will keep the parts
交叉点，但将保留零件
coming from the bottom object
来自底部的对象
so with the X on top of the circle the
因此，由于X在圆圈的顶部，
parts of the x that stick out are
X中突出的部分是
removed but with a circle on top the X
已删除，但在X的顶部有一个圆圈
will determine the cutout and
将决定裁剪和
non-overlapping circle parts are removed
删除不重叠的圆形部分
cut path is for cutting strokes this
此切割路径用于切割笔划
means the fill will be removed and the
意味着填充将被移除，并且
stroke of the apple is cut into pieces
苹果的笔划被切成了碎片
fracture is the same as intersection and
断裂等同于相交和
division but now all parts remain
分裂，但现在所有部分都保持不变
to create a heart shape I drag a
要创建心形，我要拖动一个
rectangle and round the corners I press
长方形和圆角我按下
the space bar to go to the select tool
要转到选择工具的空格键
when I click on the rectangle again I
当我再次点击该矩形时，我
can rotate the object when I hold Ctrl I
当我按住Ctrl I键时可以旋转对象
can rotate in 15 degree increments I
可按15度增量旋转
will rotate 45 degrees I duplicate the
将旋转45度，我复制
shape I click on the flip object
我点击翻转对象的形状
horizontal icon I hold Ctrl and move
水平图标我按住Ctrl键并移动
them a bit closer I select them both and
再靠近一点，我把它们都选上
go to path fracture by holding down the
按住鼠标右键转到Path Fracture
ALT key I can select the heart shape I
Alt键I可以选择心形I
go to path union now I can remove the
转到Path Union，现在我可以删除
parts I don't need and finally you have
我不需要的部分，你终于有了
flattened which is the same as fracture
扁平化，这与骨折相同
but will only make Cuts there where
但只会在以下情况下进行削减
lines are visible
线条可见